And we greatly appreciate the surge of officers that enhance what MPD has been able to do in this city.
The most significant thing that we are highlighting today is the area of crime that was most troubling for us in 2023.
Now, we have driven it down over the last years, but I'm going to get my glasses so I can make sure.
Put the glasses on, yeah, so you can see the lies clearer.
The difference between this period, this 20-day period of this federal surge and last year represents a 87% reduction in carjackings in Washington, D.C.
We know that when carjackings go down, when use of gun goes down, when homicide or robbery go down, neighborhoods feel safer and are safer.
So this surge has been important to us for that reason.
What is there to say in this broad is a piece of work, but whoo!
There are the only three options here for why this lady be acting like this.
Either one, she just hates y'all.
And by y'all, I mean D.C.
Two, she hates everybody.
Three, she got some type of situation that she's trying to Eric Adams her way out of, if you catch my drift.
Or four, she done run up that tab at that hairdresser and she just knows she got to stay on point with these fools so that she can pay it off.
Because she stay with a new hairdo.
And it's not just because she black.
It's not here for a new hairdo.
So that's pretty good.
But in the beginning, the definition for roles that do so that she can pay it off.
All we have to do so is that we need to do that.
So again, the machine for the grieving of I just wanted to do that.
I think that seems a bit of entryway, particularly in my already.
It seems to be important.
Because I spent a bit of a hallway I don't know when this time is his first conversation.